

portfolio@briankturner.me | 469-580-5248 | Red Oak, TX 75154

## **Summary**

Offering over 5+ years of progressive experience in owning web-based projects from concept and design through testing, implementation and client updates. Diligent about producing exceptionally clean, strong and secure code. Successful at achieving browser, device and operating system compatibility objectives while satisfying client desires and producing robust, sophisticated designs. Organized and motivated employee eager to apply time management and organizational skills in various environments. Seeking entry-level opportunities to expand skills while facilitating company growth. Flexible hard worker ready to learn and contribute to team success.

#### Skills

- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- DOM manipulation
- Integrating third-party libraries (jQuery, Bootstrap)
- RESTful APIs
- JSON, AJAX

- Node.js
- MYSQL, NoSQL, and MongoDB
- Converting traditional applications into progressive web applications (PWAs)
- JavaScript (data structures, algorithms)
- Python, Java, C#, and AWS (Amazon Web Services)

# Experience

SMU Full stack Bootcamp | Dallas, TX
Student

11/2021 - Current

- Completed assigned duties and consistently produced high volume of work to support daily business needs.
- Contributed to development, planning and completion of project initiatives.
- Edited resources to reflect current information.
- Balanced school, extracurricular activities and work along with healthy social connections and personal health.
- Utilized resources and asked for support when needed.

Texas CDL Prep | 1320 Beach Drive, TX **Owner** 

01/2017 - Current

- Oversaw deployment, configuration and documentation procedures for Texas CDL Prep.
- Drafted whitepapers, user manuals, implementation documentation and support base entries to reduce customer tickets and customer service expenses.
- Designed mobile applications for Apple and Android platforms.

### **Education and Training**

SMU Full Stack Development Bootcamp | Dallas Full Stack Development Completion Certificate (SMU) in Fullstack Development Expected in 02/2022

#### Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

• https://bkturner1220.github.io \*Github Profile\*

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/brian-turner-1923b8177 \*LinkedIn Profile\*
- https://briankturner.me \*Website Portfolio\*

# Certifications

• Certified Full stack Developer, SMU Coding Bootcamp - 2021-2022